The URL that we built looks good and the JSON
string from the server also looks good. However, it still is
one long string. Let's look at it more carefully to see
what data we should extract from it. In order to make
sense of the string that comes back from the server, we
can put it through a JSON formatter or a JSON prettifier.
If you Google for those terms, you'll be able to find
a helpful tool such as this one. Here, we pasted the
result of the web query. Then, it formatted the output for
us showing us the hierarchy of these elements. Now based on
the wireframes that you saw for the Sunshine app, can you
tell us which of these leaf nodes we care about extracting?
Even though we will have to traverse through parent nodes, for
the purposes of the quiz on the next screen, we're just
looking at the leaf nodes. Make your selections below on which
attributes we'll need in order to display the list of forecasts